What?
Aren't you about to…
beat me up?
No, I won't
I just…
I won't judge
so just be honest
- Do you like me?
- Huh?
I wasn't sure at first
but I'm starting
to feel more certain
What is he
talking about?
He's got it all wrong
I'll still treat you
like a friend
so don't worry
Does that mean
he'll be my friend?
Then should I just say
that I am?
No
I need to correct him
Of course not
I had
a girlfriend before
Sorry I gave you
the wrong idea
Is that so?
Let's go inside
Hey, Lee Hyeon-wu!
But it's true that
I've been
acting friendlier
because I want to
get close to you
I'm saying…
I don't mind that
you misunderstood
so you shouldn't
worry either
Got it? Huh?
Got it?
It's seriously not true
I told you, I like girls
Everyone from my
middle school knows
I had a girlfriend!
Same middle school…
What the f***?
It's not true
Hey, is it true?
The rumor's
spreading everywhere
I heard it's because
of what you said
Is it true?
It was just a joke
So it wasn't true
but people think
he's gay now
Hey
It was just
a misunderstanding
Who cares?
Everyone's going to
make fun of him
Poor kid